strangeloopgames.com 2014-07-08

# Privacy Policy | Strange Loop Games

## Your Privacy

Strange Loop Games, Inc. (“Strange Loop Games” or “we”) is committed to protecting the privacy rights of our online users (“users” or “you”). This Online Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) has been crafted to inform you as to the ways we collect, store, use, manage, and, in certain circumstances, share the information you provide in connection with any Strange Loop Games game, application, or web site (“Service”). Please note that the scope of this Privacy Policy is limited to only information collected by Strange Loop Games through use of the Service.

By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may amend the Privacy Policy from time to time, and we encourage you to consult the Privacy Policy regularly for changes.

## What information do we collect?

Strange Loop Games’s primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the Service and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the Service.

When you install any of the Strange Loop Games’s games or applications, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through www.facebook.com (“Facebook”) and/or other social network(s) in accordance with the policies and terms of Facebook and/or other social network(s). We store your first and last name, gender, and other basic profile information (such as your Facebook user identification number). We do not store your date of birth, addresses, telephone numbers, or credit card information.

We may store your email address and use it in conjunction with your name and other information to notify you of new product releases and features, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. Those emails will contain links for preference management and where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further emails.

Some information that we collect, such as your high scores, game progress, statistics, in-game messages, virtual items you have purchased in the service, and other session usage activity may be displayed to other users, for the purpose of fulfilling the game-play and game design requirements of the Service.

We also collect “usage information,” when necessary, that may be linked to your personal information, that helps us improve the experience of all our users, but is not disclosed publicly. Usage information that is logged on our servers includes, but is not limited to, browser type, program errors and exceptions, interface clicks, game screen captures, game-play and purchasing habits, and other game events. We use this information, for example, to discover bugs and other problems, make the service easier to use and more fun, and discover users who cheat or abuse other users.

Any time you access the Service, we may collect aggregate information including but not limited to internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of this activity (“aggregate information”). We use this aggregate information to better tailor the Service to your interests, to provide you more efficient customer support, and to overall enhance the Service.

## How do we protect your information?

Our game software and databases are hosted on a secured server that does not allow access to the public. Firewalls, passwords, and encryption technology protect the information about our users that we store. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties (for example, “hackers”) will never be able to overcome those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. Also please note that email and messaging systems are not considered secure, so we discourage you from sending us personal information through these mediums.

## What about “cookies”?

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk, generally to quickly identify a user’s computer and to “remember” things about the user’s visit, such as your preferences or your log-in information. The Service sends cookies to your computer when you access or view content of the Service. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personal information for purposes such as improving the quality of our service, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the Service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time through your browser, although you may not be able to access or use features of the Service.

## Will Strange Loop Games disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

In all cases of data access and collection, the information you provide will not be disclosed, rented, leased, loaned, sold, or otherwise voluntarily distributed to unaffiliated third parties and will be used solely for the purpose of providing you with and improving the Service.

We may disclose information about you to our partners in order to provide the Service, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Service, to communicate with you about the Service, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, and to enhance your experience on the Service. However, we do not give our partners an independent right to share this information. Due to our contractual obligations with these third parties and the need to share information to deliver and support the Service, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing information (whether personal information or non-personal information) with these third parties. Strange Loop Games, certain of its partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the information that you transmit to the Service to provide the Service and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Service. We do not provide any personal information to third-party advertising companies on a non-aggregate basis. Our system and the third-party advertising technology may use aggregate information, non-personal information, Strange Loop Games’s cookies on your hard drive and your use of the Service to target advertisements. In addition, advertisers may use other third- party advertising technology to target advertising on other sites. If advertisements are served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer.

## Will you disclose my information if required by law?

Strange Loop Games may release user information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Strange Loop Games, our users, or others. Note that Strange Loop Games is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that Strange Loop Games may receive.

Additionally, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, customer information may be transferred to Strange Loop Games’s successor or assignee, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

## Others’ Information

You may decide to provide us with another person’s personal information such as email address so that the person may be invited to join the Service. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join the Service or receive content from the Service. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above.

## Third-Party Privacy Policies

Because our games may be integrated with third-party web sites such as facebook.com, some of the interactions you have while playing our game may be interactions with these third-party sites and not Strange Loop Games’s software.

For more information on how Facebook and its applications protect your privacy, and how you can remove the ability for applications to access your personal information, please go to: [facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

Strange Loop Games may provide links to other web sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Strange Loop Games has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Strange Loop Games cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

## Can I change or delete my information?

You may review, update, correct or delete any personal information by changing the applicable information in your profile page on Facebook and/or other social network(s). If you completely delete all this information, your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we are not legally obligated to retain the record.

## What is your policy regarding children?

The Service is not geared toward children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information we will delete such information from our files as quickly as possible.

## Questions and Feedback

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please contact us via our [contact page](http://www.strangeloopgames.com/about-us/).

## Thank you for playing!

This Privacy Policy was last modified on November 28th, 2013.
